<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss>
<channel>
	<title>Newzee Tutorial</title>
	<link>www.github.com</link>
	<description>NewZee</description>
	<item>
		<title>1. Welcome to Newzee</title>
		<link>http://github.com/Tommertom/newzee</link>
		<pubDate>NA</pubDate>
		<description>
		Great stuff, this newsreader. It allows you to quickly go through a number of sources
		and it will keep track of what you have seen or not. You can add custom feeds from 
		Twitter, Instagram, RSS feeds and Pinterest!		
		</description>
	</item>
    <item>
		<title>2. Tap me!</title>
		<link>http://github.com/Tommertom/newzee</link>
		<pubDate>NA</pubDate>
		<description>
		By tapping on an item, you will see any message that is provided by the feed.
		You can then like the item, to save it, open the deeplink or read further.
		There is a social sharing option: right upper corner, tap the arrow to share
		this newsitem with friends and family.Finished reading the popup? Just tap anywhere.
		</description>
	</item>
	 <item>
		<title>3. Slide me to the right!</title>
		<link>http://github.com/Tommertom/newzee</link>
		<pubDate>NA</pubDate>
		<description>
		By sliding to the left, you can do actions on this specific newsitem. You can
		delete the item, mark it as favorite, or share it.
		</description>
	</item>
	 <item>
		<title>4. Slide me to the left!</title>
		<link>http://github.com/Tommertom/newzee</link>
		<pubDate>NA</pubDate>
		<description>
		Sliding the left gives you options on the specific feed related to the item: delete all
		items from the feed and remove the feed from the settings. This feature allows you
		to quickly scan new feeds for relevance, and remove them when needed.
		</description>
	</item>
	 <item>
		<title>5. Hold and press this item</title>
		<link>http://github.com/Tommertom/newzee</link>
		<pubDate>NA</pubDate>
		<description>
		Doing a "long press" directly moves you to the link provided by the newsitem.
		</description>
	</item>
	 <item>
		<title>6. Doing a manual refresh</title>
		<link>http://github.com/Tommertom/newzee</link>
		<pubDate>NA</pubDate>
		<description>
		You can do a manual refresh by pulling the screen down (from the top item onwards).
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>7. What are these things on the bottom of the screen???</title>
		<link>http://github.com/Tommertom/newzee</link>
		<pubDate>NA</pubDate>
		<description>
		To the bottom of the screen, you can find three icons: scroll page up, delete all items (except for the 
		ones marked as favorite) and scroll page up. 
		When there are no items available, these icons are no longer available. A feed settings option is 
		made available.
		</description>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>8. Before you continue... click me</title>
		<link>http://github.com/Tommertom/newzee</link>
		<pubDate>NA</pubDate>
		<description>
		Before you continue, make sure you delete this feed from your settings (remember: slide left, delete feed), 
		otherwise, you continue to see this tutorial.
		</description>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>